James R. "Jim" Dunnam papers, Inclusive: 1982-2011, Bulk: 1996-2010
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Legislative, 1982-2010; 4
  - 75th Session, 1996-2002; 2
    - Topical, 1996-1997; 6
      - Four Year State University, Killeen, TX, 1997 March-May (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Harris County Metro Transit Authority, 1997 March-April (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Health, General, 1997 February-April (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Helmet Law, 1997 January-April (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Higher Education, General, 1997 February-May (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Home Equity, 1997 March-May (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Hypnotherapy, 1997 November-December (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - Insurance, General, 1997 March-May (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - Kingwood Annexation, 1997 March-May (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - New Taxes For Sports Stadium, HB 92, 1997 February-June (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - PAC Contributions, 1997 June 1 (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - Post-Tenure Review, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - Private School Vouchers, 1997 March-May (Box 26, Folder 15)
      - Property Tax, 1997 March (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - Real Estate, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 17)
      - Sales Tax On Commercial Rents, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 18)
      - Shock Therapy, HB 570, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 19)
      - State Employee Pay, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 20)
      - Statute Of Limitations Of Child Assault, 1997 January-April (Box 26, Folder 21)
      - Teacher Retirement, 1997 February-April (Box 26, Folder 22)
      - Texas Credit Union, 1997 April (Box 26, Folder 23)
      - Texas Municipal Retirement System, 1997 February (Box 26, Folder 24)
      - Texas State Technical College, General, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 25)
      - Texas State Technical College, Correspondence, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 26)
      - Texas State Technical College, Dunnam Speeches, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 27)
      - Texas State Technical College, System Administration (1 of 2), 1997 (Box 26, Folder 28)
      - Texas State Technical College, System Administration (2 of 2), 1997 (Box 26, Folder 29)
      - Tort Reform, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Transfer University Of Central Texas To Texas A&M University, 1997 April-May (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Tuition Waver For Public Educator’s Children, 1997 March-May (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Video Gambling, 1997 April-May (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - 76th Session, 1997-2000; 3
    - General, 1999; 1
      - Dunnam Attendance, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Dunnam’s House and Senate Bills Summary, 1999 May 18 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Photo Index of 76th Legislature, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Session in Review, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Voting History, 1999 June (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1997-1999; 2
      - General, Condolence Letters, circa 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - General, Congratulation Letters, circa 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - General, Get Well Letters, circa 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - General, House Composite Photo, 1997 October (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - General, Invitations, 1998 August 24 (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - General, Thank You Letters, circa 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - General, Texas House of Representatives General Election, 1998 November 16 (Box 27, Folder 16)
      - A, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 17)
      - B (1 of2), 1999 (Box 27, Folder 18)
      - B (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 27, Folder 19)
      - C (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 27, Folder 20)
      - C (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 27, Folder 21)
      - D, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 22)
      - E, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - F, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - G (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - G (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - H (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - H (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - I-J, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - K (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - K (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - L, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - M (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - M (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - N, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - O, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - P (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - P (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - Q, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - R, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - S (1 of 3), 1999 (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - S (2 of 3), 1999 (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - S (3 of 3), 1999 (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - T, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - U, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - V, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - W (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 29, Folder 14)
      - W (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - X-Y, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Z, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - House Bills, 1999; 3
      - HB 1395, Allowing Annexed Residents to Vote in a Municipal Election, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - HB 1459, Facilities & Services for the Elderly of Disabled in Municipal Hospital Authorities, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - HB 1460, Lobbying Activities, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - HB 1461, Oversight and Public Access to the Supreme Court and Court of Criminal Appeals, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - HB 1991, Appeal Of Court Orders And Judgements Relating To Arbitration, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - HB 3490, Audits Of Insurance Defense Council, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Judicial Rules (1 of 3), 1999 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Judicial Rules (2 of 3), 1999 (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - Judicial Rules (3 of 3), 1999 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Senate Bills, 1999; 4
      - CSSB 560, Telecommunications Bill Publication, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - SB 4, Public School Appropriations, General, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 14)
      - SB 4, Correspondence, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 15)
      - SB 4, Conference Committee Report, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 16)
      - SB 4, House Floor Amendments, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 17)
      - SB 4, Legislative Budget Board, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 18)
      - SB 4, Side-by-Side Analysis, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 19)
      - SB7, Key Features of Texas Electric Utility Restructuring, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 20)
      - SB 717, Video Copy Report/Request, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Joint Resolutions, 1999; 5
      - HCR 103, Waco 150th Anniversary, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 22)
      - HJR 54, Rulemaking Power Of The Supreme Court, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 23)
      - HR 349, State Home for Dependent and Neglected Children 80th Anniversary, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Topical, 1997-2000; 6
      - 1999 Special Olympics Sponsorship, 1999 February (Box 30, Folder 25)
      - Abstinence Education Programs, 1997 September (Box 30, Folder 26)
      - ADA Compliance, 1998 September (Box 30, Folder 27)
      - Advanced Warning Traffic Signs for South Bosque Elementary, 1998 March-June (Box 30, Folder 28)
      - Alcohol Advertising in Texas Parks and Wildlife Department, 1999 February (Box 30, Folder 29)
      - Alcoholic Beverage Consumption by Minors, 1998-1999 (Box 30, Folder 30)
      - Amateur Radio Operators, HB 1345, 1999 February (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - American Legion Boy’s State Convention, 1998 June (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Annexation of Rural Areas, 1998 October (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Authorized Blood Alcohol Content for Adults, HB 210, 1999 March (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Bank Boxes, 1998 October (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Bilingual Education, 1999 April (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Builder Licensing, 1999 March (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Cable Monopoly, 1999 May 5 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Candidate Survey, 1998 July-September (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Capitol Police Officers, 1999 April 21 (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Cen-Tex Hispanic Chamber of Commerce, 1998 July (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Charter Schools, 1999 April (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Child Support, 1998 July-November (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Childcare Provider Training, 1999 February (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - City of Groesbeck, c. 1999 (Box 31, Folder 15)
      - Committee on Criminal Jurisprudence, 1998 July (Box 31, Folder 16)
      - Committee on Higher Education, 1997 January-October (Box 31, Folder 17)
      - Community Based Alternative Program, 1999 March (Box 31, Folder 18)
      - Construction Contractors, 1999 May 10 (Box 31, Folder 19)
      - Death Penalty, 1999 April (Box 31, Folder 20)
      - Dental Care, 1998 July 6 (Box 31, Folder 21)
      - Department of Public Safety, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 22)
      - Divorce Laws, 1997 September (Box 31, Folder 23)
      - DWI, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 24)
      - Dyslexia, 1999 April 13 (Box 31, Folder 25)
      - Educational Materials, 1998 November 23 (Box 31, Folder 26)
      - Election, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 27)
      - Election, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 28)
      - Electric Company Competition, 1999 April (Box 31, Folder 29)
      - Emergency Medical Services & Trauma Care System Fund, HB 1920, 1999 March (Box 31, Folder 30)
      - Equitable Pay System for Nurses, 1998 November (Box 31, Folder 31)
      - Family Code, 1998 October (Box 31, Folder 32)
      - Federal Health Insurance, 1998 October (Box 31, Folder 33)
      - Health Care, 1998 September (Box 31, Folder 34)
      - Health & Safety Code, 1998 October 12 (Box 31, Folder 35)
      - Hog Dog Hunting, HB 1389, 1999 February-March (Box 31, Folder 36)
      - Home Equity Lending & Veterans’ Homes, 1997 November-1999 January (Box 31, Folder 37)
      - Injured Worker Medical Care, 1999 April (Box 31, Folder 38)
      - Inmate Correspondence, 1999 March (Box 31, Folder 39)
      - Inmate Prison Transfer, 1997-1998 (Box 31, Folder 40)
      - Inmate Visitation, 1998 September (Box 31, Folder 41)
      - Judicial Redistricting, 1997 December (Box 31, Folder 42)
      - Lawsuit, Johnson v. City of Waco, 2000 April (Box 31, Folder 43)
      - Lubbock Chamber of Commerce, 1999 February 8 (Box 31, Folder 44)
      - Medicaid, 1998 July (Box 31, Folder 45)
      - McLennan County Courthouse, 1998 August 26 (Box 31, Folder 46)
      - Mental Disabilities, 1998 October (Box 31, Folder 47)
      - Mental Retardation Authority (MRA), 1999 (Box 31, Folder 48)
      - Motor Vehicles Propelled by Liquefied Gas, HB 3421, 1997 December (Box 31, Folder 49)
      - Municipal Court Fees Subcommittee, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 50)
      - Online Database of Sexual Predators, 1999 January (Box 31, Folder 51)
      - Operation of Redemption Equipment, 1999 March-April (Box 31, Folder 52)
      - Optometry, 1999 February 1 (Box 31, Folder 53)
      - Parole Requests, 1998 July-December (Box 31, Folder 54)
      - Photographic Control Systems, 1999 April 19 (Box 31, Folder 55)
      - Potential Legislation, 1997 October-December (Box 31, Folder 56)
      - Private Property Rights, 1999 February (Box 31, Folder 57)
      - Private School Vouchers, 1998 December-1999 April (Box 31, Folder 58)
      - Providence Health Center, 2000 February-April (Box 31, Folder 59)
      - Public School Funding, 1997 December 1999 April (Box 31, Folder 60)
      - Public School Health Care, 1998 September (Box 31, Folder 61)
      - Religious Freedom Restoration Act (RFRA), 1997 November (Box 31, Folder 62)
      - Requiring Community Service for Public High School Students, HB 17, 1999 February (Box 31, Folder 63)
      - Rohypnol, 1998 April-May (Box 31, Folder 64)
      - Rules for Discovery, 1998 April-May (Box 31, Folder 65)
      - Sale of Mixed Beverages, 1999 April 6 (Box 31, Folder 66)
      - Same-Sex Marriage, 1998 July-October (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - School Counselor Salary, circa 1999 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Small Business Stationary Source Assistance Program Compliance Advisory Committee, 1998 November 18 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Social Security, 1998 January (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Social Work, 1999 February 22 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - State Scholarships and Loans for Private Career Schools, 1999 January-February (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - State Textbook Review Panels, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Subcommittee on Court Fees, 1998 May-July (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Subcommittee on Indigent Legal Services, 1998 July 9 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Teacher Retirement, 1998 November-1999 February (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Teacher Salary, 1998-1999 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Texas Association of School Boards, 1997 December 5 (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Texas Business Advocate, 1997 December-1998 July (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - Texas Campaign for Women’s Health, 1999 February (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - Texas Commission on Alcohol and Drug Abuse, 1998 July (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - Texas Department of Criminal Justice, 1999 February (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - Texas Department of Health, 1997 November (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - Texas Department of Human Services, 1998 July-September (Box 32, Folder 18)
      - Texas Family Land Heritage, 1998 January (Box 32, Folder 19)
      - Texas Flag Presentations, 1998 July-December (Box 32, Folder 20)
      - Texas Higher Education Coalition, 1998 February (Box 32, Folder 21)
      - Texas Higher Education Coordinating Board, 1997 September (Box 32, Folder 22)
      - Texas Historical Commission, Tonkawa Park, 1998 June (Box 32, Folder 23)
      - Texas Organization of Rural & Community Hospitals (TORCH), 1998 October (Box 32, Folder 24)
      - Texas Soil & Water Conservation, 1998 July 13 (Box 32, Folder 25)
      - Texas Worker Compensation Commission, 1997 November-1998 October (Box 32, Folder 26)
      - Texas Youth Commission, 1997 December 1 (Box 32, Folder 27)
      - Traffic Offenses, 1999 March (Box 32, Folder 28)
      - Tuition Equalization for Out of State Scholarships, 1998 February 6 (Box 32, Folder 29)
      - Vehicle Insurance and Motor Fuel Sold, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - 77th Session, 2000-2002; 4
    - General, 2000-2001; 1
      - Dunnam Attendance, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 31)
      - Dunnam Voting History, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 32)
      - House Research Organization Daily Floor Report, 2001 March (Box 32, Folder 33)
      - Legislature Selections, 2000 November (Box 32, Folder 34)
      - Natural Resources Committee, 2001 March (Box 32, Folder 35)
      - Oath of Office, 2000 December (Box 32, Folder 36)
      - Photo Index of the 77th Legislature, c. 2000 (Box 32, Folder 37)
      - Record Votes, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 38)
      - Results of Primary Candidates for Office, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 39)
      - Session Overview, 2001 May (Box 32, Folder 40)
      - 78th Candidacy Plans, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - House Bills, 2001-2002; 2
      - Agent Runner Bill, Uniform Athletes Agent Act, General, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 42)
      - Agent Runner Bill, Uniform Athletes Agent Act, Bill History, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 43)
      - Agent Runner Bill, Uniform Athletes Agent Act, Draft, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 44)
      - Charter Schools, Preliminary Draft, undated (Box 32, Folder 45)
      - HB 5, Operation Of A Motor Vehicle Under The Influence Of Alcohol, General (1 of 3), 2001 (Box 32, Folder 46)
      - HB 5, General (2 of 3), 2001 (Box 32, Folder 47)
      - HB 5, General (3 of 3), 2001 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - HB 5, Alabama Department Of Transportation, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - HB 5, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - HB 5, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - HB 5, Correspondence & Memos, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - HB 5, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - HB 5, News Media, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - HB 6, General (1 of 2), 2001 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - HB 6, General (2 of 2), 2001 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - HB 6, Amendments, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - HB 6, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - HB 6, Committee Report, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - HB 6, Comparison of Legislation and Implementing Rules, undated (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - HB 6, Conference Committee Report (1 of 2), 2001 (Box 33, Folder 14)
      - HB 6, Conference Committee Report (2 of 2), 2001 (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - HB 6, Conference Committee Report, undated (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - HB 6, Executive Summary, circa 2002 (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - HB 6, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - HB 6, House Committee on Public Education, 2001 March 20 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - HB 6 Information, Timeline, 2001-2002 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - HB 6, Information For HB6 On Charter Schools, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - HB 6, Open-Enrollment Charter Schools, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - HB 6, Revisions and Recommendations, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - HB 6, Substitute, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - HB 6, Talking Points, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - HB 539, Authorization Of Court To Appoint A Guardian For A Minor Who Has Entered Into A Contract, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - HB 963, Authorizing Insurance Of Revenue Bonds For State Technical College System, General, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - HB 963, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - HB 963, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - HB 963, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - HB 963, Talking Points, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - HB 964, Release Of Confidential Patient Information By Physician, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - HB 964, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - HB 964, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 17)
      - HB 964, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 18)
      - HB 965, Eligibility Requirements For Lottery Sales Agent License, General, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 19)
      - HB 965, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 20)
      - HB 965, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 21)
      - HB 965, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 22)
      - HB 965, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 23)
      - HB 1039, Southern Dairy Compact, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 24)
      - HB 1212, Tuition Payments For Students In Summer Sessions, General, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 25)
      - HB 1212, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 26)
      - HB 1212, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 27)
      - HB 1212, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 28)
      - HB 1212, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 29)
      - HB 1379, Uniform Electronic Transactions Act, General, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 30)
      - HB 1379, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 31)
      - HB 1381, Special License Plates For Members Of Municipal Governments, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 32)
      - HB 1381, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 33)
      - HB 1381, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 34)
      - HB 1381, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 35)
      - HB 1382, Insurance Carrier Info Required In Workers’ Compensation, General, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 36)
      - HB 1382, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 37)
      - HB 1382, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 38)
      - HB 1382, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 39)
      - HB 1382, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 40)
      - HB 1383, Attorneys Employed Or Contracted To Insurers, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 41)
      - HB 1383, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 42)
      - HB 1383, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 43)
      - HB 1383, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 44)
      - HB 1384, Termination Of Agreements With Insurance Agents, General, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 45)
      - HB 1384, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 46)
      - HB 1384, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - HB 1384, Facsimile Transmittal, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - HB 1384, Memorandum, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - HB 1384, Testimony, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - HB 1384, Witness List, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - HB 1433, Audits Of Insurance Defense Council, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - HB 1433, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - HB 1433, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - HB 1433, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - HB 1451, Public Access To Supreme Court & Court Of Appeals, General, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - HB 1451, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - HB 1451, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - HB 1451, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - HB 1451, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - HB 1464, Peremptory Challenge Of Juror In Criminal Case, General, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 15)
      - HB 1464, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 16)
      - HB 1464, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 17)
      - HB 1464, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 18)
      - HB 1470, Enrichment Curriculum Requirements, General, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 19)
      - HB 1470, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 20)
      - HB 1470, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 21)
      - HB 1470, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 22)
      - HB 1470, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 23)
      - HB 1594, Allowing A Train To Stand On A Street, Railroad Crossing, Or Highway, General, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 24)
      - HB 1594, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 25)
      - HB 1594, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 26)
      - HB 1594, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 27)
      - HB 1594, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 28)
      - HB 1740, Appeal Of Court Orders And Judgment Relating To Arbitration, General, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 29)
      - HB 1740, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 30)
      - HB 1740, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 31)
      - HB 1740, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 32)
      - HB 1740, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 33)
      - HB 1741, Appeal Of Insurance Of Protective Order, General, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 34)
      - HB 1741, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 35)
      - HB 1741, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 36)
      - HB 1741, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 37)
      - HB 1741, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 38)
      - HB 1742, Grants For Public Schools Adopting Innovative Educational Programs, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 39)
      - HB 1742, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 40)
      - HB 1742, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 41)
      - HB, 1742, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 42)
      - HB 1817, Planning And Decision Making Process Of School Districts, General, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 43)
      - HB 1817, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 44)
      - HB 1817, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 45)
      - HB 1817, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 46)
      - HB 1817, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 47)
      - HB 1854, Penalty For Operating Motor Vehicle Without A Driver’s License, General, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 48)
      - HB 1854, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 49)
      - HB 1854, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 50)
      - HB 1854, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 51)
      - HB 1854, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 52)
      - HB 2019, Notice To Personal Auto Insurance Policy Holders Of The Consumer Bill Of Rights, General, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 53)
      - HB 2019, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 54)
      - HB 2019, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 55)
      - HB 2019, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 56)
      - HB 2057, Allowing Retirees Of The Teacher Retirement System To Be Employed As Bus Drivers, General, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 57)
      - HB 2057, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 58)
      - HB 2057, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 59)
      - HB 2057, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - HB 2057, Talking Point, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - HB 2169, Disqualification Of Judges Or Justices Of The Peace To Sit In A Criminal Case, General, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - HB 2169, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - HB 2169, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - HB 2288, Release Of A Criminal Defendant On Bail Pending Appeal, General, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - HB 2288, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - HB 2288, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - HB 2288, Fiscal Note, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - HB 2387, Procedures Involved In Intoxication Offenses, General, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - HB 2387, Bill Analysis, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - HB 2387, Bill Text, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 12)